Guide to the Cornell University Cooperative Extension records, 1915-2009.
Cornell University Cooperative Extension records, 1915-2009.
- Series III. Publications
  - Cornell Publications
    - Gardening, Nutition, and Home Environment Catalog 04-05, 2004 (Box 54)
    - Catalog of Publications and Audiovisuals - 1995 (Box 54)
    - Catalog of Publications and Audiovisuals - 1993 (Box 54)
    - Creative Marketing (Box 54)
    - Growing African Violets, 1978 (Box 54)
    - A Day in Day Care: A Program for Two-Year-Olds, 1991 (Box 54)
    - Bee Balm at Littleflowers Postcard By Bruce Wang (Box 54)
    - Caraway Crackers at Sage Cottage Postcard By Bruce Wang (Box 54)
    - Edible Flowers Postcard By Bruce Wang (Box 54)
    - Strategies for Managing Pests in and Around the Home By Carolyn Klass, 1996 (Box 54)
    - When A New York State Resident Dies Without a Will By Wiegand and Coughlan, 1986 (Box 54)
    - Overwhelmed with Nutrition Information (Box 54)
    - Portable Kerosene Heaters, 1982 (Box 54)
    - Impact Statements, 1988, 1997, 1998-04 (Box 54)
    - "Working With New Yorkers", 1996-09 (Box 54)
    - Executive Summary of Final Report for "Healthy Families" and "Building Blocks for Toddlers", 1996 (Box 54)
    - "Children, Youth, Families, and Communities, Excellence in Extension Education", 1999-10 (Box 54)
    - Highlights from 1999 Study "Speak Out" (Box 54)
    - Survey of New York State Residents, 1999 (Box 54)
    - Choosing High Quality Child Care-No. 2-5, 2000 (Box 54)
    - Helping New Yorkers Improve Their Lives and Communities, 2009 (Box 54)
    - New Cultivation Tools for Mechanical Weed Control in Vegetables By Jed Colquhoun, 1997 (Box 55)
    - Grower's Guide to Cabbage Pest Management in New York By Petzoldt C H, 1991 (Box 55)
    - Fundamentals of a Sea Grant Extension Program, 2001 (Box 55)
    - 4-H Club Secretary Handbook, 2002 (Box 55)
    - Nutrient Management: Crop Production and Water Quality By Stu Klausner (Box 55)
    - Estimating a Mass Nutrient Balance By Stu Klausner (Box 55)
    - Water and the Soil By Nancy M Trautmann, 1985 (Box 55)
    - Dairy Management: Body Condition Scoring: A Useful Tool for Dairy Herd Management By B L Perkins, 1985 (Box 55)
    - Dairy Management: Troubleshooting Your Herd with the Body Condition Scoring System By B L Perkins, 1987 (Box 55)
    - Dairy Management: Protein in Dairy Nutrition By C J Sniffen, 1981 (Box 55)
    - Integrated Pest Management for the Deer Tick (Packs of 25) By Carolyn Klass, 1993 (Box 55)
    - Home-Grounds-Gardens: Fact Sheet Set (Box 55)
    - Home-Grounds-Garden: Techniques for Propagation of Plants for Interior Decoration By Raymond T Fox, 1981 (Box 55)
    - Indoor Gardening By Ernest F Schaufler, 1986 (Box 55)
    - Indoor Gardening-Dish Gardens and Terrariums, 1970-09 (Box 55)
      Reprint
    - Indoor Gardening-Creating Plaques from Dried Material, 1976-03 (Box 55)
    - Indoor Gardening-Corsages from Dried Flowers, 1975-01 (Box 55)
      Revised
    - Indoor Gardening-Corsages from Garden Flowers, 1966-05 (Box 55)
    - Young People's Guide to Landscaping By Ernest F Schaufler, 1985 (Box 55)
    - Backyard Maple Syrup By Alex Dickson, 1991 (Box 55)
    - Recreational Access and Owner Liability By Tommy L Brown, 1995 (Box 55)
    - Trees: Dead or Alive By Marianne E Krasny, 1991 (Box 55)
    - Know Your Trees By F E Winch Jr, 1990 (Box 55)
    - Know Your Trees (older edition) By F E Winch Jr, 1980 (Box 55)
    - Sugar Bush Management By Robert R Morrow, 1981 (Box 55)
    - What about Waste? By Jean F Bonhotal, 1990 (Box 55)
    - Growing Button Mushrooms By Juliet E Carroll, 1989 (Box 55)
    - Turfgrass Disease List and Identification Key for New York State By R W Smiley, 1985 (Box 55)
    - Herbaceous Perennials: Diseases and Insect Pests By Margery Daughtrey, 1992 (Box 55)
    - Clean Water Starts with You: Nutrients and Sediments (Box 55)
    - What Happens Next? By Margo Hittleman, 1992 (Box 55)
    - Stress on the Farm, 1983 (Box 55)
    - Talking with Kids about AIDS: Teaching Guide and Resource Manual By Jennifer Tiffany, 1993 (Box 55)
    - The Physical Environment of a Child Care Center: What Parents Should Know By Maxwell Lorraine, 1994 (Box 55)
    - Designing Child Care Settings By Maxwell Lorraine, 1998 (Box 55)
    - Family Activities and Children's Schoolwork By Maxwell E Lorraine, 2000 (Box 55)
    - Cane Seats for Chairs By Ruth B Comstock, 1994 (Box 55)
    - Splint Seats for Chairs By Ruth B Comstock, 1988 (Box 55)
    - Waste Management at the Construction Site By Laquatra Joseph, 2002 (Box 55)
    - Household Cleaning Products: What About Substitutes? By Ann Lemley, 1992 (Box 55)
    - Disposal of Household Hazardous Wastes By Linda Waganet, 1989 (Box 55)
    - Fiber Facts By Frances Kozen, 1999 (Box 55)
    - Simple Gifts By Doreen Greenstein, 2000 (Box 55)
    - Apparel Industry Outreach By Frances Kozen, 2000 (Box 55)
    - Growing: Infants 0-12 Months (Packs of 10) By Jennifer Birckmayer, 1999 (Box 55)
    - Growing: Infants 0-12 Months (Spanish)(Packs of 10) By Jennifer Birckmayer, 1999 (Box 55)
    - Growing: Toddlers 1-3 Years (Packs of 10) By Jennifer Birckmayer, 1996 (Box 55)
    - Growing: Toddlers 1-3 Years (Spanish) (Packs of 10) By Jennifer Birckmayer, 1996 (Box 55)
    - Growing: Preschoolers 3-5 Years (Packs of 10) By Jennifer Birckmayer, 1996 (Box 55)
    - Growing: Preschoolers 3-5 Years (Spanish)(Packs of 10) By Jennifer Birckmayer, 1996 (Box 55)
    - Northeast Regional Food Guide (Set of 9 Guide/Fact Sheets) By Nutritional Sciences, 2002 (Box 55)
    - Sisters in Health: A Nutrition Program for Women By Tracy J Farrell, 1999 (Box 55)
    - Farm Families Fact Sheets (#1-5) By Jane W McGonigal, 1989 (Box 55)
    - Agricultural Engineering Facts: Producing Sweet Sorghum Syrup in New York State By Mariann E Bischoff, 1992 (Box 55)
    - Fire Blight: Its Nature, Prevention, and Control By T van der Zwet, 1991 (Box 55)
    - Modern Agriculture: Its Effects on the Environment By Nancy M Trautmann, 1985 (Box 55)
    - Groundwater: What It is and how to Protect It By Nancy M Trautmann, 1985 (Box 55)
    - Nitrogen: The Essential Element By Nancy M Trautmann, 1989 (Box 55)
    - Nitrate: Health Effects in Drinking Water By Nancy M Trautmann, 1985 (Box 55)
    - Pesticides and Groundwater: A Guide for the Pesticide User By Nancy M Trautmann, 1989 (Box 55)
    - Pesticides: Health Effects in Drinking Water By Nancy M Trautmann, 1985 (Box 55)
    - A Manual for Pleasure Trail Riding By S W Sabin, 1982 (Box 55)
    - Cutting Meat By G H Wellington, 1984 (Box 55)
    - Dairy Goat By W F Brannon, 1981 (Box 55)
    - Agritourism in New York State By Duncan Hilchey, 1993 (Box 55)
    - Basics of Housecleaning and Home Care By Grace E Tasker, 1982 (Box 55)
    - Contaminants in Sport Fish: Managing Risk By Ken Gall and Mike Voiland, 1990 (Box 55)
    - A Guide to coastal Erosion Process By Charles O'Neil Jr., 1985 (Box 55)
    - Structural Methods for Controlling Coastal Erosion By Charles O'Neil Jr., 1986 (Box 55)
    - Cornell Cooperative Extension Publications Catalog, 1988 (Box 55)
    - Cornell Cooperative Extension Publications Catalog, 2001 (Box 55)
    - Cornell Cooperative Extension Publications Catalog, 2002 (Box 55)
    - Common Pest Flies Found in the Urban/Rural environment and Their Biological Control Agents By Kaufman and Rutz, 2000 (Box 55)
    - Marine Science at Work By Kent and Greene, 1995 (Box 55)
    - Marketing The Small Lodging Business By Chad Dawson, 1988 (Box 55)
    - Maintaining Coastal Erosion Control Structures By Charles O'Neil Jr., 1984 (Box 55)
    - Integrated Pest Management of Disease By Margery Daughtrey, 1996 (Box 55)
    - Fish Contaminints and Human Health By Michael Duttweiler, 1978 (Box 55)
    - Banded Grape Bug By Timothy Martinson, 1998 (Box 55)
    - Functional Kitchens By Rose E. Steidl, 1980 (Box 55)
    - Moving Toward Fitness By Joanne Tarbox, 1983 (Box 55)
    - What's a teacher to Do? Child Abuse By Lorraine M. Wolverton, 1987 (Box 55)
    - Low Temperature Injury to Apples in the Champlain Valley 1980-1981 by McNicholas and Forshey, 1982 (Box 55)
    - Establishment of European Lady Beetle in New York State by Tauber, Nechels, Obrycki (Box 55)
    - Actionwear: Clothing for Fitness, 1985 (Box 55)
    - Nutrition and Your Health: dietary guidelines for Americans (Box 55)
    - Clothing for People With Special Needs, 1987 (Box 55)
    - Guidelines for the Effective Use of Floating Tire Breakwaters, 1983 (Box 55)
    - Handling your Catch, 1986 (Box 55)
    - Marketing Your Charter Boat Enterprise: Putting Relationships to Work, 1987 (Box 55)
    - Managing Risk at Your Waterfront Facility, 1989 (Box 55)
    - New York's Great lakes Recreational Weather, 1986 (Box 55)
    - Care and Handling of Charter Boat Fishing Customers, 1988 (Box 55)
    - Getting Started in Shellfish Mariculture, 1984 (Box 55)
    - Preparing Those "Forgotten Fish" for Your Dinner Table, 1978 (Box 55)
    - Equipment Protection through Oil Analysis, 1981 (Box 55)
    - Electrical Submetering in Marinas, 1987 (Box 55)
    - Extension Workers Creed (Box 58, Folder 1)
    - Publications-Highlights, 2003-2008 (Box 58, Folder 2)
    - "Outdoor Living: Clothing and Equipment", 1974 (Box 58, Folder 3)
    - "Concerns of the Aging Nutrition and Health Related Statistical Data", 1976 (Box 58, Folder 4)
    - "A Neighborhood Approach: Nutrition Education", 1979 (Box 58, Folder 5)
    - "Understanding Children Through Play", 1981 (Box 58, Folder 6)
    - "Taking Care of Two-Nutrition for Moms and Babies"-English and Spanish, 1993 (Box 58, Folder 7)
    - "Improving Our Diet: Nutritional Recommendations for Hispanics Living in the United States", 1996 (Box 58, Folder 8)
    - "More From Your Money"-in Spanish (Box 58, Folder 9)
    - "My Money, Myself"-Leader's Guide (Box 58, Folder 10)
    - "More Responsibility and Older Children"-Members Guide (Box 58, Folder 11)
    - Caring for Young Children- Teen Notebook- Florence Cherry, 1980-1989 (Box 64, Folder 16)
    - Caring- A Guide for 4-H Leaders and 4-H Members in 4-H Community Development Projects- Florence Cherry, 1980-1989 (Box 64, Folder 17)
    - Publications: You and Your Family series; "Making the Most of the Eighties; Cornell Cooperative Extension, into the 80's; Guide to Develop Effective Program Committees (1980); Citizen Advisory Committees: A Guide for Members and Potential Members, by Alan Hahn- 1981/82 Cornell Cooperative Extension Directory, 1981-1982 (Box 44, Folder 21)
    - Resources for Parents and Others who Care About Children-Varopis Topics, 1980-1994 (Box 64, Folder 18)
    - Caring for Young Children in the Home- Written by the Northeast 4-H Family Life/ Personal Development Committee, 1981 (Box 64, Folder 19)
    - What are Children Like? - Written by Northeast 4-H Family Life/ Personal Development Committee, 1981 (Box 64, Folder 20)
    - Instructions for Staff and Adult Volunteers, 1981 (Box 64, Folder 21)
    - Learning is....by Jennifer Birckmayer, 1981 (Box 64, Folder 22)
    - Be a Food Detective- 4-H Leader's Guide by Martha Mapes, 1983 (Box 64, Folder 23)
    - Children's Friendships by Suzanne West, 1985 (Box 64, Folder 24)
    - Question and Answer Letter Series, 1985-1987 (Box 44, Folder 22)
    - Food and Nutrition- The Link between Health and Agriculture- Directions for the Cooperative Extension System (Box 64, Folder 25)
    - "Discipline is Not a Dirty Word"- Jennifer Birckmayer, 1987 (Box 64, Folder 26)
    - Toddler Topics by Jennifer Birckmayer, 1987 (Box 64, Folder 27)
    - Opportunities for Nutrition Education through Cornell Cooperative Extension in Metropolitan Areas- Muriel Brink, 1988-09 (Box 64, Folder 28)
    - Balancing Work and Family Life, 1988-1990 (Box 64, Folder 29)
    - Building Blocks by Jennifer Birckmayer, 1989-1993 (Box 64, Folder 30)
    - Be a Better Shopper- Instructor's Manual- Heniz Biesdorf, Lonie Stimac, Jo Swanson, Patricia Thonney (Box 64, Folder 31)
    - Teens as Parents of Babies and Toddlers, 1989 (Box 64, Folder 32)
    - Nutrition Flyers, 1990-1999 (Box 64, Folder 33)
    - Building an Understanding of Credit Services- Jeanne Hogarth, Josephine Swanson, Jane Baker Segelken, 1990-1999 (Box 64, Folder 34)
    - Better Living Pamphlets, 1990-1999 (Box 64, Folder 35)
    - Building on Understanding of Credit Services (Box 64, Folder 36)
    - Building on Understanding of Credit Services (Box 64, Folder 37)
    - Building on Understanding of Credit Services (Box 64, Folder 38)
    - Children in my Care- in English and Spanish, 1990-1999 (Box 64, Folder 39)
    - Child Care Center Connections; Family Child Care Connections; School-Age Connections- Volume 3- Issues 1-3, 1993-1994 (Box 64, Folder 40)
    - Child Care Center Connections; Family Child Care Connections; School-Age Connections- Volume 3- Issues 4-6, 1994 (Box 64, Folder 41)
    - Child Care Center Connections; Family Child Care Connections; School-Age Connections- Volume 4- Issues 1-2, 1994 (Box 64, Folder 42)
    - Child Care Center Connections; Family Child Care Connections; School-Age Connections- Volume 4- Issues 4-6, 1995 (Box 64, Folder 43)
    - Child Care Center Connections; Family Child Care Connections; School-Age Connections- Volume 5- Issues 1-3, 1995-1996 (Box 64, Folder 44)
    - Child Care Center Connections; Family Child Care Connections; School-Age Connections- Volume 5- Issues 4-6, 1996 (Box 64, Folder 45)
    - Child Care Center Connections; Family Child Care Connections; School-Age Connections- Volume 6- Issues 1-4, 1996-1997 (Box 64, Folder 46)
    - Child Care Center Connections; Family Child Care Connections; School-Age Connections- Volume 7- Issues 1-4, 1997-1998 (Box 64, Folder 47)
    - Child Care Center Connections; Family Child Care Connections; School-Age Connections- Volume 8- Issues 1-4, 1998-1999 (Box 64, Folder 48)
    - Child Care Center Connections; Family Child Care Connections; School-Age Connections- Volume 9- Issues 1-4, 1999-2000 (Box 64, Folder 49)
    - Child Care Center Connections; Family Child Care Connections; School-Age Connections- Volume 10, 2001 (Box 64, Folder 50)
    - Patterns of Change- A Report of the Cooperative Extension System Strategic Planning Council, 1991-03 (Box 65, Folder 1)
    - Cornell Cooperative Extension Addresses Critical Issues, 1992, 1993 (Box 65, Folder 2)
    - A Study of Extension Association Publications: Current Situation, Future Needs and Recommendations, 1992-08 (Box 65, Folder 3)
    - Training Staff in Child Care Programs for Infants and Toddlers- Jennifer Birckmayer, Polly Spedding, 1993 (Box 65, Folder 4)
    - Talking with Kids About Aids- English, 1993 (Box 65, Folder 5)
    - Talking with Kids About Aids- Spanish, 1993 (Box 65, Folder 6)
    - New York State Cloverbuds, 1993 (Box 65, Folder 7)
    - Healthy Families- appendices, 1994 (Box 65, Folder 8)
    - State 4-H Curriculum Development Status Report, 1994 (Box 65, Folder 9)
    - Take Charge of your Money- manual, 1994 (Box 65, Folder 10)
    - "Get the Goods, Not the Garbage"- A Waste Reduction Education Project for Limited Resource Families, 1994 (Box 65, Folder 11)
    - "More From Your Money" (revised), 1994 (Box 65, Folder 12)
    - Statewide Program Committees, 1993,1994 (Box 65, Folder 13)
    - Feeding Your Baby, The First Year of Life- Joan Clanton, 1995-05 (Box 65, Folder 14)
    - Discipline is Not a Dirty Word- Jennifer Birckmayer (revised), 1995 (Box 65, Folder 15)
    - In the Bag; Kitchen Science for Kids- by Pat Thonney, Tracy Farrell, Charlotte Coffman, 1995-1996 (Box 65, Folder 16)
    - In-Touch Science Foods and Fabrics by Pat Thonney, Tracy Farrell, Charlotte Coffman, 1996 (Box 65, Folder 16A)
    - In-Touch Science Chemistry and Environment by Nancy Trautmann and John Terry, 1999 (Box 65, Folder 16A)
    - In-Touch Science Plants and Engineering by Marcia Eames-Sheavly, Doreen Greenstein, Raylene Ludgate and Dad Tennessen, 1999 (Box 65, Folder 16B)
    - "Suggested Resources in Parent Education", 1996 (Box 65, Folder 17)
    - Parent-Adolescent Communication, 1996 (Box 65, Folder 18)
    - Cornell Cooperative Extension at Work- brochure and flyers, The Cornell Connection- A Historical Perspective- brochure, Committed to Excellence- Executive Summary, 1991, 1999, 2000,2001 (Box 65, Folder 19)
    - Parent-Adolescent Communication- by Florence Cherry, 1996 (Box 65, Folder 20)
    - Caring for Kids, 1997-09 (Box 65, Folder 21)
    - Resources for Families, Educators and Caregivers, 2000, 2001 (Box 65, Folder 22)
    - Advancing Youth Development (AYD) Networker, 2001 (Box 78, Folder 14)
      Winter
    - List of Publications and Videos, 2002 (Box 65, Folder 23)
    - Pamphlets on Family Food - Labeled ML 6, 8, 9, 11-13, Undated (Box 89, Folder 28)
  - External Publications
    - Value-Free Objective Educators-Do They Exist? (Box 47, Folder 50)
    - Nassau County 4-H Story-by Jean Louise Kempton, 1957 (Box 80, Folder 13)
    - The Cooperative Extension Service Today, 1958 (Box 47, Folder 51)
    - The Beginning of Extension Programs and Their Development, 1959 (Box 47, Folder 52)
    - Early Forms of Extension Work in Agriculture and Home Economics, 1962 (Box 47, Folder 53)
    - The Extension Service Partnership With County Supporting Agencies in New York, 1962 (Box 47, Folder 54)
    - FOCUS: Extension Home Economics, 1966 (Box 47, Folder 55)
    - The Cooperative Extension Service in Transition, 1979 (Box 47, Folder 56)
    - Cooperative Extension in New York State, 1982 (Box 47, Folder 57)
    - A Catalyst for Change - The Extension Service, 1983 (Box 47, Folder 57A)
    - Extension in the 80s;Cornell Cooperative Extension in the 80s, 1983, 1981 (Box 47, Folder 57B)
    - Public Policy Education in Extension Home Economics, 1984 (Box 47, Folder 58)
    - Regaining Farm Profitability in America, 1984 (Box 47, Folder 59)
    - Public Policy Education: An Issues Approach, 1985 (Box 47, Folder 60)
    - Food and Nutrition, 1986 (Box 47, Folder 61)
    - Revitalizing Rural America, 1986 (Box 47, Folder 62)
    - Extension in Transition, 1987 (Box 47, Folder 63)
    - New Directions for a New Decade, 1989 (Box 47, Folder 64)
    - Northeast Network News, 1990-1999 (Box 1, Folder 40)
    - Preparing for the Next Century, 1990 (Box 47, Folder 65)
    - Strategic Directions of the Cooperative Extension System, 1990 (Box 47, Folder 66)
    - Plight of the Young Child, 1991 (Box 47, Folder 67)
    - The 21st Century Extension Professional in the Midst of Organizational Change, 1992 (Box 47, Folder 68)
    - A Brief Summary of the Organization of the National Association of State Universities and Land-Grant Colleges, 1994 (Box 47, Folder 69)
    - Focus on the Future, 1994 (Box 47, Folder 70)
    - PIE: Public Issues Education, 1994 (Box 47, Folder 71)
    - Shaping Our Future, 1994 (Box 47, Folder 72)
    - Collaboration Framework: Addressing Community Capacity, 1995 (Box 47, Folder 73)
    - Framing the Future, 1995 (Box 47, Folder 74)
    - Framing the Future of Cooperative Extension-A System of Partnerships, 1995 (Box 47, Folder 75)
    - Charting the Course for the Cooperative Extension System Federal Agenda, 1996 (Box 47, Folder 76)
    - Colleges of Agriculture at the Land-Grant Universities, 1996 (Box 47, Folder 77)
    - The State and the Farmer, 1996 (Box 47, Folder 78)
    - Teaching in Land-Grant and State Universities: New Perspectives in Human Sciences, 1996 (Box 47, Folder 79)
    - Urban Extension: A National Agenda, 1996 (Box 47, Folder 80)
    - Final Report to WK Kellogg Foundation, 2001 (Box 47, Folder 81)
    - Building Political Support for Extension in the 21st Century (Box 47, Folder 82)
    - National Extension Leadership Development: Intern Class IV and V (Box 47, Folder 83)
    - What it Takes, 1991 (Box 47, Folder 84)
    - Parent Education for Families with Limited Resources, 1992 (Box 47, Folder 85)
    - Welfare Reform and the Role of Extension Programming, 1994 (Box 47, Folder 86)
    - Albany- NE Youth at Risk, 1995 (Box 47, Folder 87)
    - NELD Conference, 1995 (Box 47, Folder 88)
  - Papers, Articles and Flyers
    - Extension open forum comments-Fred B. Morris presiding (Box 58, Folder 29)
    - Farm Bureau-papers, statements (Box 58, Folder 28)
    - History of Extension, 1930-1949 (Box 86, Folder 8)
    - History of New York State Extension Service-Papers, Articles, 1939-1969 (Box 86, Folder 9)
    - Extension Service papers by Carl Ladd; Alfred Charles True; Liberty Hyde Bailey; C.B. Smith, 1936-1944 (Box 58, Folder 26)
    - "The Dust Bowl: Agricultural Problems and Solutions", 1940 (Box 80, Folder 11)
    - Survey of Extension Work in Urban Areas in the Northeast, 1949 and 1950 (Box 80, Folder 12)
    - "Program Pointers", 1943-1962 (Box 70, Folder 5)
    - "Small Fry", 1944-1946 (Box 70, Folder 6)
    - Extension Service papers - no authors, 1950-1959 (Box 58, Folder 24)
    - The Expansion of the Extension Service Program in New York State, 1954-08-29 (Box 58, Folder 26-A)
    - "Organization and Administration of the New York State Cooperative Extension Service"-by James Preston and Lucinda Noble, 1958-1959 (Box 41, Folder 4)
    - "A Supervisory Plan in Program Development"- by Lucinda Noble, 1959 (Box 41, Folder 5)
    - "Cornell's Role and Opportunity in Extension and Public Service Functions," "Cornell and the New Social Legislation," " Cornell's Rose in Extension," "New Federal Legislation Offers New Opportunities for Cornell University" -all by R.F. Risley and A.A. Johnson, 1960-1969 (Box 86, Folder 10)
    - History of Costume-Papers, Articles, 1960-1969 (Box 86, Folder 31)
    - The First Agricultural Adjustment Administration, 1961 (Box 80, Folder 14)
    - Memos concerning the Home Economist-by Vera Caulum, 1962-1963 (Box 86, Folder 11)
    - Administration of the New Department of Agriculture-by Gladys Baker, 1962 (Box 80, Folder 15)
    - Protecting the Soil Farm Incomes and Food Supplies, 1935-1940-by Gladys Baker, 1962 (Box 80, Folder 16)
    - "The Role of the Professional Home Economist in Informal Adult Education As Student, As Teacher" by Vera Caulum, 1966 (Box 86, Folder 12)
    - Food Group - Flyers, 1970-1979 (Box 1, Folder 34)
    - Focus on Food Flyers - Chautauqua County, 1970-1979 (Box 89, Folder 27)
    - Good Nutrition: An Investment in Your Family's Future - Flyers, 1980-1989 (Box 1, Folder 35)
    - Eater's Digest - New York City High School Teen Nutrition Newsletter, 1980-1981 (Box 1, Folder 36)
    - Milestones in the Evolution of the Cooperative Extension Service, 1978, 1982 (Box 86, Folder 13)
    - Agricultural Industry: Its Impact and Future: What It Is. What it Can Be, by David Call, 1983-03 (Box 46, Folder 1)
    - Agricultural Impact Program background and Intro, by James Preston; Agricultural Perceptions and Language, by D. Guy Burns; Structure of Agriculture, by Fred Buttle and Bernard Stanton, 1983 (Box 46, Folder 2)
    - Agriculture and the Local Economy: A Review of Regional Economic Concepts and Their Relation to the Local Food and Agriculture System, by David Lee; Farm Enterprise Data, by Donald White; Agribusiness Data, by Donald White, 1983 (Box 46, Folder 3)
    - Real Property Tax Data, by Donald White; Farm and Agribusiness Economic Potentials, by Donald White; Agricultural Careers: Where Are We? Where Do We Go?, by Robert Tenney; Agent Roles, Leadership Styles, Program Impact, by David Smith; Applying Marketing Concepts to Agricultural Advancement, by Robert Topor; Alternative Strategies; Resource Materials: Bibliography, 1983 (Box 46, Folder 4)
    - Agricultural Industry: Its Impact and Future-material from other years, 1984-1985 (Box 46, Folder 5)
    - "What Makes and Effective Extension Specialist"-Gerald White, 1999 (Box 77, Folder 35)
    - Extension Home Economics in Saratoga County - by Mary Jane Ellis, 2002 (Box 68)